Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
♪My heart shattered, withered into pieces♪
♪تحطم قلبي، ذبل إلى قطع♪
♪Yet I still can't find a trace of you♪
♪ولكنني لا أزال غير قادر على العثور على أي أثر لك♪
♪Like a whale drowning in the cracks of the deep sea♪
♪مثل حوت يغرق في شقوق البحر العميق♪
♪Thinking of you, I lose myself completely♪
♪أفكر فيك، وأفقد نفسي تمامًا♪
♪My heart shattered, withered into pieces♪
♪تحطم قلبي، ذبل إلى قطع♪
♪Humbly, I still long to search for you♪
♪بكل تواضع، ما زلت أتوق للبحث عنك♪
♪Screaming as I fall into the darkest abyss♪
♪أصرخ وأنا أسقط في الهاوية المظلمة♪
♪Echoing back is only the tide of loneliness♪
♪العودة إلى الوراء ليست سوى موجة الوحدة♪
♪Overestimating myself♪
♪المبالغة في تقدير نفسي♪
=Marry Him in Her Place=
=تزوجيه مكانها=
=Episode 21=
=الحلقة ٢١=
(Liang's Apothecary)
(صيدلية ليانغ)
What happened?
ماذا حدث؟
They came in
لقد دخلوا
and just grabbed everything of value.
واستولى على كل شيء ذي قيمة.
Who would dare cause trouble in the apothecary in broad daylight?
من يجرؤ على إثارة المشاكل في الصيدلية في وضح النهار؟
The shareholders.
المساهمون.
The shareholders?
المساهمون؟
Things have gone downhill
الأمور ساءت
ever since Master Liang passed.
منذ وفاة المعلم ليانغ.
Things finally started turning around after you came back.
بدأت الأمور تتحسن أخيراً بعد عودتك.
But yesterday,
لكن بالأمس،
the founding shareholders suddenly announced
أعلن المساهمون المؤسسون فجأة
they were pulling out as a group.
كانوا ينسحبون كمجموعة.
They demanded 5,000 silver dollars.
طالبوا بخمسة آلاف دولار فضي.
I checked the books.
لقد راجعت الكتب.
Even if we emptied every account,
حتى لو قمنا بتفريغ جميع الحسابات،
we could scrape together maybe 3,000 at most.
يمكننا جمع 3000 على الأكثر.
That's far from enough.
وهذا ليس كافيا.
Showing up at daybreak to cause a mess,
الظهور عند الفجر لإحداث فوضى،
it could only be them.
لا يمكن أن يكونوا إلا هم.
You're pulling out?
هل ستنسحب؟
Why?
لماذا؟
You still have the nerve to ask why?
هل لا زال لديك الشجاعة لتسأل لماذا؟
The profits have dropped
انخفضت الأرباح
to a pathetic state.
إلى حالة يرثى لها.
We only put money in
نحن نضع المال فقط
because we respected your father.
لأننا كنا نحترم والدك.
With your father gone,
مع رحيل والدك
the reason for our partnership is gone as well.
لقد زال سبب شراكتنا أيضاً.
You think a little girl like you
تظنين أن فتاة صغيرة مثلك
can run a business?
هل يستطيع إدارة مشروع تجاري؟
Stop dreaming.
توقف عن الحلم.
I am the rightful head of the Liang family now.
أنا الرئيس الشرعي لعائلة ليانغ الآن.
You should watch your tone.
عليك أن تنتبه لنبرة صوتك.
Also,
أيضًا،
do not drag your past dealings with my father into this.
لا تزجّ بتعاملاتك السابقة مع والدي في هذا الأمر.
If not for him, you'd still be out there wondering where your next meal was coming from.
لولا وجوده، لكنت لا تزال هناك تتساءل من أين ستأتي وجبتك التالية.
Just give us
فقط أعطنا
the money
المال
and we'll leave.
وسنغادر.
And if I refuse?
وإذا رفضت؟
Then, we'll help ourselves.
ثم سنساعد أنفسنا.
The apothecary
الصيدلي
couldn't have been making money every year.
لا يمكن أن يكون قد حقق أرباحاً كل عام.
All of you acting in such perfect unison
جميعكم تتصرفون بتناغم تام
couldn't have happened by itself.
لم يكن ليحدث ذلك من تلقاء نفسه.
Someone must be pulling strings.
لا بد أن هناك من يحرك الخيوط.
You've made plenty from the Liang family.
لقد جنيت الكثير من عائلة ليانغ.
Give me one month.
أعطني شهراً واحداً.
If I can't fill the gap
إذا لم أستطع سد الفجوة
and turn things around
وقلب الأمور رأسًا على عقب
within that time,
خلال تلك الفترة،
do whatever you want.
افعل ما تشاء.
If I can,
إذا استطعت،
we continue as usual
نواصل العمل كالمعتاد
and pretend this never happened.
وتظاهر بأن هذا لم يحدث أبداً.
I'll even add 1% profit as compensation.
بل سأضيف ربحًا بنسبة 1% كتعويض.
Do not let her sweet talk fool you.
لا تدع كلامها المعسول يخدعك.
And here comes the puppeteer.
وها هو محرك الدمى قادم.
There are 5,000 silver dollars in this case.
يوجد في هذه الحقيبة 5000 دولار فضي.
I'll buy
سأشتري
all
الجميع
your shares.
أسهمك.
Mr. Lin, are you serious?
سيد لين، هل أنت جاد؟
Do I have a deal
هل لدي اتفاق؟
or not?
أم لا؟
Yes.
نعم.
I'll do it.
سأفعل ذلك.
Me too.
أنا أيضاً.
Count me in.
اعتبرني من ضمنهم.
You people must have a death wish,
يبدو أنكم تتمنون الموت،
taking money from Chengyun Society.
أخذ أموال من جمعية تشنغيون.
I don't know what Mr. Lin promised you,
لا أعرف ما الذي وعدك به السيد لين،
but from what I know,
لكن حسب علمي،
the Chengyun Society's money comes with a price.
أموال جمعية تشنغيون لها ثمن.
You might keep it now,
يمكنك الاحتفاظ به الآن،
but can you keep it forever?
لكن هل يمكنك الاحتفاظ به إلى الأبد؟
How many have taken a bit of profit
كم منهم حقق بعض الأرباح؟
only to cough it back ten or a hundred times over?
ثم يسعلها مرة أخرى عشر مرات أو مئة مرة؟
Have you not heard the stories? You don't even need to look far.
ألم تسمع القصص؟ لا تحتاج حتى إلى البحث بعيداً.
Surely you all know how the Dai family lost
لا شك أنكم جميعاً تعرفون كيف خسرت عائلة داي
their 13 shops.
متاجرهم الـ 13.
Miss Liang, you seem to think you know Chengyun Society
آنسة ليانغ، يبدو أنكِ تعتقدين أنكِ تعرفين جمعية تشنغيون
so well.
حسنا.
Even if I don't know
حتى لو لم اعرف
the Chengyun Society or you,
جمعية تشنغيون أو أنت،
I'm sure the investors do.
أنا متأكد من أن المستثمرين يفعلون ذلك.
We'll return and discuss this matter.
سنعود لمناقشة هذا الأمر.
Miss Liang,
الآنسة ليانغ،
I see you're determined to do this the hard way.
أرى أنك مصمم على القيام بذلك بالطريقة الصعبة.
Men,
الرجال،
bring them all back.
أعيدوهم جميعاً.
Mayor Song has become the provincial chairman.
أصبح العمدة سونغ رئيساً للمقاطعة.
As the wealthiest merchants in Rong City, you should set an example,
بصفتكم أغنى التجار في مدينة رونغ، يجب أن تكونوا قدوة حسنة.
support the chairman's work,
دعم عمل الرئيس،
and contribute to Jiangzhou's development and defense.
والمساهمة في تنمية جيانغتشو والدفاع عنها.
We're living in turbulent times,
إننا نعيش في أوقات مضطربة،
yet you can still make money in safety.
ومع ذلك، لا يزال بإمكانك جني المال بأمان.
Learn to be grateful.
تعلم أن تكون شاكرا.
This isn't a request for donations.
هذا ليس طلباً للتبرعات.
This is robbery.
هذه سرقة.
Every business under the Lu family is covered in that agreement.
يشمل هذا الاتفاق جميع الشركات التابعة لعائلة لو .
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
I was beginning to see why your mouth gets you in trouble.
بدأت أفهم لماذا يوقعك لسانك في المشاكل.
Seems your teeth grew crooked.
يبدو أن أسنانك أصبحت ملتوية.
(Recipient: Lin Yun)
(المستلم: لين يون)
You're a sensible man, Mr. Wang.
أنت رجل عاقل يا سيد وانغ.
Come on.
تعال.
Bring in the banner.
أحضروا اللافتة.
(Presented to Mr. Wang)
(مقدمة إلى السيد وانغ)
Honored citizen of Jiangzhou,
مواطن جيانغتشو المحترم،
respected figure of Rong City.
شخصية مرموقة في مدينة رونغ.
Congratulations, Mr. Wang.
تهانينا، سيد وانغ.
Can I go now?
هل يمكنني الذهاب الآن؟
Of course. Take care.
بالتأكيد. اعتنِ بنفسك.
You can earn back lost money.
يمكنك استعادة الأموال المفقودة.
However, if you lose your life,
لكن إذا فقدت حياتك،
you lose everything.
لقد خسرت كل شيء.
You're shameless!
أنت عديم الحياء!
What's the big idea? What are you doing to me?
ما الفكرة الكبيرة؟ ماذا تفعل بي؟
Stay the night.
اقضِ الليلة.
Let us clean that head of yours
دعنا ننظف رأسك
and fix your attitude.
وعدّل موقفك.
Excuse us
عذرا
if things get a bit harsh.
إذا ساءت الأمور قليلاً.
Enough.
كافٍ.
I don't want a dead man.
لا أريد رجلاً ميتاً.
He'll frighten my fish.
سيخيف أسماكي.
What's the matter?
ماذا جرى؟
Have you lost your voice already?
هل فقدت صوتك بالفعل؟
What have you turned into?
إلى ماذا تحولت؟
You clearly got the wrong idea about me.
من الواضح أنك فهمت الأمر بشكل خاطئ.
I was never a good person.
لم أكن شخصًا جيدًا أبدًا.
Take a good look.
ألقِ نظرة جيدة.
This is who I am.
هذه هي شخصيتي.
I don't believe you.
أنا لا أصدقك.
This isn't who you are.
هذه ليست شخصيتك الحقيقية.
You're only doing this because you resent me.
أنت تفعل هذا فقط لأنك تحمل ضغينة تجاهي.
Liang Yi,
ليانج يي,
you give yourself too much credit.
أنت تمنح نفسك الكثير من التقدير.
Although, I suppose
مع ذلك، أعتقد
I should thank you.
ينبغي عليّ أن أشكرك.
If it weren't for you,
لولاك،
I wouldn't have reunited with a father who has this much power.
لم أكن لألتقي مجدداً بأب يملك كل هذه السلطة.
I should have returned to him long ago
كان ينبغي عليّ أن أعود إليه منذ زمن طويل
and made full use of my talents.
واستفدت استفادة كاملة من مواهبي.
Who do you think you are?
من تظن نفسك؟
What gives you the right?
ما الذي يعطيك الحق؟
What gives?
ماذا يعطي؟
Do not test my limits.
لا تختبر حدودي.
Understand?
يفهم؟
I can kill you anytime I want.
أستطيع قتلك متى أشاء.
(It's my fault.)
(هذا خطأي.)
(I'm the one who pushed him into the abyss.)
(أنا من دفعه إلى الهاوية.)
(Memorial Tablet of Husband Song Zhichu, offered by his widow Liang Yi)
(لوحة تذكارية للزوج سونغ تشيتشو، مقدمة من أرملته ليانغ يي)
(Rong City Municipal Hall, Rong City Police Bureau)
(مبنى بلدية مدينة رونغ، مكتب شرطة مدينة رونغ)
Isn't that the daughter of the Liang family?
أليست هذه ابنة عائلة ليانغ؟
No, it's Mrs. Lin.
لا، إنها السيدة لين.
What?
ماذا؟
Have you not heard?
هل لم تسمع؟
She's the real Miss Liang,
إنها الآنسة ليانغ الحقيقية،
the wife of Song Zhichu.
زوجة سونغ تشيتشو.
I can't tell what kind of show those two families are putting on.
لا أستطيع أن أحدد نوع العرض الذي تقدمه هاتان العائلتان.
(Donation Agreement, Recipient: Lin Yun)
(اتفاقية التبرع، المستفيد: لين يون)
Boss, Miss Liang has gone to the Song Residence.
سيدي الرئيس، لقد ذهبت الآنسة ليانغ إلى مقر إقامة عائلة سونغ.
I, Zhichu's widow, have come to keep vigil.
لقد جئتُ، أرملة تشيتشو، لأبقى في حالة تأهب.
The Liang family has been persecuted by Chengyun Society,
تعرضت عائلة ليانغ للاضطهاد من قبل جمعية تشنغيون.
our property taken by force.
تم الاستيلاء على ممتلكاتنا بالقوة.
I beg you to help me, Father.
أرجوك يا أبي أن تساعدني.
I, Zhichu's widow,
أنا، أرملة Zhichu،
beg you to uphold justice for me, Father.
أتوسل إليك يا أبي أن تنصفني.
We'll talk inside.
سنتحدث في الداخل.
(Memorial Tablet of Husband Song Zhichu, offered by his widow Liang Yi)
(لوحة تذكارية للزوج سونغ تشيتشو، مقدمة من أرملته ليانغ يي)
(Righteous Spirit)
(الروح الصالحة)
Where is she?
أين هي؟
In the mourning hall.
في قاعة العزاء.
That girl has guts.
تلك الفتاة شجاعة.
She really came up with a move that underhanded.
لقد لجأت فعلاً إلى حركة ملتوية للغاية.
Let me handle her.
دعني أتعامل معها.
If she's so eager to be a Song daughter-in-law,
إذا كانت متلهفة للغاية لأن تصبح زوجة ابن لعائلة سونغ،
then let her join Zhichu on the other side.
ثم دعها تنضم إلى تشيتشو على الجانب الآخر.
Yun,
الذي - التي،
I trust that you won't go soft on her.
أثق أنك لن تتساهل معها.
(Righteous Spirit)
(الروح الصالحة)
(Memorial Tablet of Husband Song Zhichu, offered by his widow Liang Yi)
(لوحة تذكارية للزوج سونغ تشيتشو، مقدمة من أرملته ليانغ يي)
Let me go!
دعني أذهب!
Get lost.
اغرب عن وجهي.
Mr. Lin,
السيد لين،
I was lawfully married to Song Zhichu.
كنت متزوجة بشكل قانوني من سونغ تشيتشو.
Is it wrong for me to keep vigil for my own husband?
هل من الخطأ أن أسهر على زوجي؟
Stop putting on an act.
توقف عن التمثيل.
You think Song Ming will defend you?
أتظن أن سونغ مينغ سيدافع عنك؟
Of course, he won't.
بالطبع، لن يفعل.
Even if he kills me,
حتى لو قتلني،
he can't silence the whole city.
لا يستطيع إسكات المدينة بأكملها.
Everyone saw what just happened.
الجميع رأى ما حدث للتو.
He'll have you disappear without a trace.
سيجعلك تختفي دون أن تترك أثراً.
And you'd be the one to do it for him, wouldn't you?
وأنتِ من ستفعلين ذلك من أجله، أليس كذلك؟
Go on, then.
هيا بنا إذن.
Dispose of me without leaving a trace.
تخلص مني دون أن تترك أثراً.
You can do it right now.
يمكنك فعل ذلك الآن.
Just say I hanged myself in grief
قل فقط أنني شنقت نفسي من شدة الحزن
before my husband's tablet.
قبل جهاز زوجي اللوحي.
Liang Yi,
ليانج يي,
do you have a death wish?
هل لديك رغبة في الموت؟
No, I want to live.
لا، أريد أن أعيش.
But you won't have the Liang family
لكنك لن تجد عائلة ليانغ
unless you step over my body.
إلا إذا تخطيت جسدي.
For the Liang family, you'd betray me
ستخونني من أجل عائلة ليانغ
and sacrifice yourself.
وضحّي بنفسك.
What would
ماذا سيكون
your father think if he could see you now?
ماذا يظن والدك لو كان بإمكانه رؤيتك الآن؟
If you want to survive,
إذا كنت تريد البقاء على قيد الحياة،
make your performance convincing.
اجعل أداءك مقنعاً.
♪Raise the big screen, start your pretentious performance♪
♪ارفع الشاشة الكبيرة، وابدأ أدائك المتكلف♪
♪The most foolish gambler♪
♪أغبى مقامر♪
♪Would treat love as prey, caring nothing♪
♪أعامل الحب كفريسة، لا أهتم بأي شيء♪
♪You pretend to be innocent, yet the red wounds are vivid in my mind♪
♪تتظاهر بالبراءة، لكن الجروح الحمراء واضحة في ذهني♪
♪Such a hypocritical gift♪
♪هذه هدية منافقة♪
♪Victory is revealed too quickly♪
♪النصر يتكشف بسرعة كبيرة♪
♪I treated you as my salvation♪
♪عاملتك كخلاصي♪
♪You treated me as a toy♪
♪عاملتني كدمية♪
♪And we both fall into endless loneliness♪
♪وكلا منا سقط في الوحدة التي لا نهاية لها♪
♪I loved too deeply♪
♪لقد أحببت بعمق شديد♪
♪Your methods are too cruel♪
♪طرقك قاسية جدًا♪
♪Once devotion is desecrated, only waiting for your disgrace♪
♪بمجرد تدنيس الإخلاص، لن تنتظر سوى عارك♪
♪I treated you as my salvation♪
♪عاملتك كخلاصي♪
♪You treated me as a toy♪
♪عاملتني كدمية♪
♪And we both fall into endless loneliness♪
♪وكلا منا سقط في الوحدة التي لا نهاية لها♪
♪I loved too deeply♪
♪لقد أحببت بعمق شديد♪
♪Your methods are too cruel♪
♪طرقك قاسية جدًا♪
♪Once devotion is desecrated, only waiting for your disgrace♪
♪بمجرد تدنيس الإخلاص، لن تنتظر سوى عارك♪
♪Curtain call♪
♪استدعاء الستار♪